[music]
>> It's a It's It's time It's time for the
man you all came to see. Um it's a It's
a pleasure to bring him to the stage and
in a moment of sincerity, if I may, um
stand up is really hard and it's really
hard when you start out. You don't
really know what you're doing at all.
And so uh this guy, he's not only been a
mentor to me, but he's been a better
friend and he's always checked in on me
throughout my entire stand-up journey.
So uh it's it's means a lot that I get
to be here hosting for him tonight.
>> [applause and cheering]
>> Okay, that was Now, fuck all that.
Now we're going to be funny again.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay, this guy this guy he has a lot of
credits. He He travels the country doing
stand-up. He's been seen on Kill Tony,
the Apollo Theater, and he is the heart
and soul of the Dayton comedy scene. So
please make it as loud as you can. The
Ohio Kid,
>> [cheering]
[cheering]
[applause]
>> Oh my goodness. Oh my goodness.
>> [applause]
>> Y'all here, man? bitch.
>> [cheering]
[applause and cheering]
>> Thank you, man. Thank you. Thank you for
coming out, man. This is my first
live taping for a comedy special, man.
Come on, clap it up for that. Clap it
up.
>> [cheering]
>> Yeah, yeah, man.
Boy, I'm happy to be here, man.
>> [applause]
[cheering]
>> I'm happy to be here, man. Dude, filming
it here especially here at Wiley's
Comedy Club, man. You know, shit, you
know, it's cuz it's good.
Y'all know it's good to be here, man.
Life's fucked up, but it's good to just
be out here, man.
>> [laughter]
>> It's good to be in Miamisburg, Ohio.
>> Said no black guy ever. Hold up.
Oh, and nig, we done broke the record
for both niggers in Miamisburg tonight,
nigger. This is
This is never happened before,
motherfucker. This is crazy, man. And
what's crazy is Miamisburg sounds like
some nigger shit.
>> [laughter]
>> Like the name of it. That sounds like a
street that's some Martin Luther King
Boulevard for short.
But it's not. It's whiter than good
credit. It's
But we here though. People was like, why
you do it here? Cuz this is where
Wiley's Comedy Club is at, man. It's one
of my favorite clubs in Ohio, man. Come
on, clap it up for the venue. Clap it
up.
>> [applause]
>> Yeah, boy.
You know,
I will I'll say this though, just so
y'all aware, man. You know, I need y'all
to understand, all right? Every single
thing
that y'all about to hear come out
my mouth tonight on this microphone, I
need all y'all to understand. Everything
that comes out my mouth on this
microphone tonight is a
fucking joke.
I'm I'm just
I'm making it very, very clear that I am
playing around.
Okay, don't take none of this shit for
real. I don't need nobody cuz don't
cross your arms nigga, you're scaring
me. But please
I am playing around. Everything that I
say, don't take this shit for real. You
would think I wouldn't have to say that,
you know, cuz we at comedy club. Y'all
even some of y'all even looking at me
like, "Yeah, I know. That's why I'm
here, dumbass."
Like y'all
y'all looking at me like it's dumb to
tell y'all that, but I have to tell
y'all that because everybody acts like
it's just jokes, you know. They act like
they understand I'm playing around
until, you know,
after the show.
Y'all know man after the show and they
didn't like what they you know we were
saying up here as comedians man when
they didn't like what we said and they
got offended and they got mad at us man.
They'd be trying to after the show catch
us
outside
uh
in the parking lot.
And and I'm going to keep it real with
y'all man. I I weigh 70 pounds nigga.
You leave me alone.
>> [laughter]
>> You leave me alone in that god damn
parking lot. I don't want no problems in
the parking lot. I don't want none.
Leave me alone. Okay, I weigh 70 pounds
and 10 of this is jacket nigga. I swear
to god
you leave me alone. I'm a very nice
young man. I'm not violent at all. Look,
my favorite drink's Capri Sun nigga. I
swear to
I swear to god man. I I'd be chewing on
the straw right after I drink it just
like
>> [laughter]
>> just like a bitch ass nigga. Just
So I don't want no issues with nobody.
[laughter]
All right? Cuz look, my whole job as a
stand-up comic man I like to make people
feel better man. I like to I don't like
causing no issues with nobody man, you
know? And honestly, if y'all just had
the attitude everything's just playing
around, you know, we going to have a
banging ass night if y'all can do that
man. So can y'all do that for me
Brickey's Comedy Club.
>> [applause]
>> Cool man, it's cool. Now, I need y'all
to understand if I do uh
happen to still offend some of y'all
tonight, uh
I don't give a fuck.
I don't give I already I already got the
money, nigga. You know, I don't give a
fuck.
>> [laughter]
>> No, no, I'm Look, cuz I'm a I'm a
risk-taker. Well, if y'all trying to
still fight me shit, I'm a risk-taker.
I've been a risk-taker my whole life.
Look, I'm a black man Miami's where
after 9:30, nigga. I
>> [laughter]
>> don't give a fuck. No.
I like that everybody's here though,
man. It's beautiful beautiful crowd. I
like to gauge like who's all in the mix,
man, you know, but like like All right,
ladies make some noise. How many ladies
we got?
>> [cheering]
[applause]
>> All right, thank y'all coming out, man,
you know, hell yeah, you know. Now, I'm
going to go and ask this next question.
Um
All the All the crazy women make some
noise.
>> [cheering]
>> Man, that that that that wasn't in That
wasn't in Hawaii.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm going to be real cuz I'm looking at
the crowd. I'm looking at some of the
dudes next to the ladies and they're
like
>> [laughter]
>> This nigga snitching. He's like
Like, "Remember that time you cut my
tire?" You know what I mean?
>> [laughter]
>> That's great. Yeah, I'll say this
though, like crazy women, man.
Crazy women.
Something about crazy women, you know,
like I I don't I don't like how loose
the term crazy is used on women.
I don't like it. It It sometimes is damn
near slurish, you know?
>> [laughter]
>> I don't like it, you know, they'll just
throw it around. It's very dismissive,
you know, that's why some people don't
like responding to it cuz you don't know
why I'm asking, you know what
It'd be kind of fucked up, you know,
call a woman crazy. It's very dismissive
cuz if you think about it, anytime
you've ever seen a crazy woman, it's
usually because
of a man.
Now fellas, you pay attention. All the
women going mhm, they're crazy.
Nigga, that's how I get them to reveal
themselves. That's why
No, no, but for real, anytime usually,
whether it was they daddy, they uncle, a
ex, some piece of shit dude sowed the
seeds of crazy in that woman.
That's how it works. I didn't make the
rules, man. That's just how it works. If
you
If you think about it, right? All right,
women, right, are very reactionary. Now,
what does that mean? When I say
reactionary, what I mean is, right, when
you're good to a woman, she's good back
to you times 10.
But if you're bad
If you're bad to a woman, she's bad to
you back times 10.
That's how the shit works, man. I didn't
make the rules up. That's just how it
works.
And I'll say this, if there's one group
of women that are called crazy no matter
what in this country, man, it's uh no
matter what they do, whether it's
reasonable or whatever,
they're always called crazy. You know
who those group of women are? Black
women.
I don't know if you're allowed to laugh
at that, white lady, but
>> [laughter]
>> All right, nigga, that That wasn't the
punchline, nigga.
Hey, this bitch She's crazy, bro. I'm
friendly.
But no, black women, they called crazy
no matter what they do. No matter how
reasonable a black woman is, they always
called crazy, which I think is wild cuz
if I had to pick
>> [laughter]
>> I'm picking a crazy black woman over a
crazy white woman any day of the week.
Now now now some of you Caucasians look
perplexed as to why I said that.
[laughter]
But let me explain why Look, you would
think cuz think about it. Just use your
logic, right? Think about it. If you
piss off a crazy black woman, the worst
she can do
is
kill you.
>> [laughter]
>> That that's the worst she can do is
murder you and murder you in
cold blood.
That's the worst a crazy black woman can
do.
But if you piss off a crazy
white woman,
you piss off a crazy white woman, the
worst she can do is
kill you,
your whole family,
>> [laughter]
>> and and beat the case for all that shit.
That's what
That's what can occur, ladies and
gentlemen. Y'all hear me, but y'all not
listening though. Nigga.
>> [laughter]
>> Spitting facts.
At least according to then uh all these
true crime documentaries I'd be
watching.
>> [laughter]
>> Y'all Y'all know about the true Clap if
you know about the true crime
documentaries.
>> [applause]
>> Man, that true That [snorts] true crime
That true crime got me petrified of
white women, man.
Terrified of white women cuz of true
crime, man. I'm just scared of them all
the time. This shit is wild. And
actually, I did my research. The biggest
demographic for true crime documentaries
is actually
black women.
Black women love watching true crime.
They're the biggest viewership of true
crime. And I finally figured out why.
It's the only time they feel less crazy
watching these white bitches crash out.
>> [cheering]
>> Oh! god.
That white lady pissed me off. That
means she's crazy as shit. That's what I
mean. That's what I mean.
But for real, that is why they watch it
cuz these white girls be crushing
[screaming] up.
Oh my [laughter] god, man. They be
spooking me on here. The main way that
these white women be killing their
husbands in these documentaries, man,
they'll go for the the the the poison.
>> [laughter]
>> The the the the poison. They'll they'll
do the poison every time. Poison.
Poison. That girl is poison. Poison.
>> [laughter]
>> Poison.
That's how they do it, man.
And and look, first off, a black woman
using poison to kill their husband,
first off, a
>> [laughter]
>> A black woman don't got the patience for
poison.
Like, come on. She she's like, come on.
I need this nigga dead right now.
I don't got no time for this tape delay
for murder, nigga. I need results.
>> [laughter]
>> Bam. That's it. She don't
She don't got time for that shit. But
that white woman true crime be having
that time, man.
>> [laughter]
>> I be sitting on the edge of my seat like
it's a new story every time. The same
thing happens every time. [laughter]
But I'm addicted to watching it as if I
don't know what's going to happen.
>> [laughter]
>> I be sitting on the edge of my seat. How
are they going to do it? It's the same
way, man. They be changing up that life
insurance and the will and they wait it
out. [laughter]
And these true crimes, these white women
be wanting to kill their husband,
they'll wait 5 years to kill this
>> [laughter]
>> Just cuz there's like a clause in the
will or some shit. Like they they do it.
They're conniving. They wait it out. And
bro, every time
they'll eat the food and die from the
poison every time.
Every time.
>> [laughter]
>> Every fucking time. Cut on the husband
right now. Cut. That's how they die.
>> [laughter]
>> After eating the poison, man, they die
after eating the food, which I think is
wild.
Cuz anytime I've ever tasted a white
woman's casserole, I already felt like I
was being poisoned anyway.
>> [laughter]
>> I knew you would get it, white lady.
>> That's what that whole build-up was for,
nigga. Just to say y'all can't season
food, nigga.
>> [laughter]
>> That was fucked up, wasn't it?
>> So, y'all stupid.
I don't know. People All right. This is
Since we here, I mean, I don't I don't
know how many y'all are that familiar
with me or got to see me live before,
but I feel like tonight's special, man,
cuz I'm going to kind of really have
y'all, you know, get to know me and who
I am a little bit, you know, my story
and shit, cuz you know, it's a special
night.
I don't know. Some people be like, "J-
Rell, why you why you so why you so
weird and crazy, man?"
Why you so But like I said, crazy is
very slurish.
You know, I don't like that label.
There's explanations to everything, man.
Like look, I've never been able to take
things too serious Like I just have
I'm I'm fucked up, man. I have
Like look, I remember I went to middle
It's middle school. It all started in
middle school. I remember I went to
middle school on a Salem Avenue. Man,
y'all don't know know that, man. I went
to school on Salem Avenue. And I'll
never forget
the principal called all the boys down
to the cafeteria.
We was in big trouble, all of us. I
remember called us down to the
cafeteria. I remember he uh he held up a
Ziploc bag
with with a used
condom in it.
Yuck, nigga. Gross. Like it was
It was so gross. Like, y'all y'all
looking at me like it was normal. No,
this was a very [laughter] weird day.
This was not a normal day at school.
Nigga, he held it up like
>> [laughter]
>> he was holding it up like evidence.
Like,
it was creeping me out. And dude, he set
it down. He held that bag up. He was
like, "Hey,
do any of you boys
want to explain to me
why I found this
in the school library?"
Now, but before I continue,
have any of y'all ever had a friend that
you should never be looking at when
serious shit's going down?
>> [laughter]
>> Any of y'all have
I'm asking y'all. Any of y'all know?
Okay, cuz if you haven't had that
friend, nigga, that means you're that
friend. That's what
Cuz we all know these people. And boy, I
remember my friend I shouldn't have been
looking at him, but I couldn't resist. I
remember his name to this day. Name was
uh Solomon As- Sa'dullah.
>> [laughter]
>> This nigga didn't even have a name you
could take serious. Like, bro,
I stood no chance.
Remember me, I couldn't resist. I kept
trying not to look at him, but it was
like a magnetic pull that I couldn't
fight. I kept trying not to And I made
[laughter] eye contact with him.
Shouldn't have did that.
I cracked, man. I cracked. I was like,
>> [laughter]
>> Couldn't hold it in.
Boy, I shouldn't have did that, man. The
principal was pissed, man.
Man, he he yelled right at me. Looked at
me. "Hey, what the hell, Beeman? What
the hell you key-keying and ha-haing
for, huh? What the hell so god damn
funny to you, Jarrell, huh? Do you know
something about this?"
>> [laughter]
>> I remember I was like, "No, Mr. Ward. I
don't know nothing about that because
that's
a magnum."
>> [laughter]
>> He was like, "Get out of this office
[screaming] now, Beam." And I was like,
"Oh, shit."
>> [laughter]
>> And that's how I became a comedian.
Now, but if you think about it, that's
kind of fucked up, man. That's kind of
He gave me detention for for having a
small dick. That's fucked up.
>> [laughter]
>> That happened today, I could sue for
body shaming, nigga. That's
>> [laughter]
>> trying to help him solve the case.
I'll say that Some people don't believe
that that story, man. That didn't really
happen, man. You know, it didn't happen.
Couldn't believe that it couldn't
believe it didn't make the news, man.
>> [laughter]
>> But that's what's weird, man. I be
watching I I be watching the news a lot,
man. I'm weird. I be reading articles,
watching news a lot. Y'all Y'all be
watching the news in here? Y'all be
watching the news? Now See, I could tell
y'all don't watch the news cuz cuz y'all
look happy. But
that news, boy, it'd be making you go go
crazy.
Make you go crazy, that news, boy. Man,
no matter what type of news you watch,
man, you did make you get all fucked up,
man, cuz that's how it's designed to
make you go go rage out and go crazy,
man. But I
watch all of it.
>> [laughter]
>> Even shit I don't believe, I read it. I
don't care. I consume it all, man. I
read a story the other day that I could
not believe. I read a headline that said
that there is an epidemic of men
falling in love
with their AI girlfriends.
Nigga, did y'all just hear what I just
said?
Y'all looking at me like that was a
normal sentence I just composed. What
the
What the fuck y'all looking at me like,
"Well, please continue." No.
That's a weird reality we're in in 2026,
man. And nobody thought that was fake. I
could tell by how It was real, of
course. It's real, men falling in love
with their AI girlfriends.
And you would think all these men are
incels or living with their mom and
shit. No, don't make assumptions.
>> [laughter]
>> No, man. A lot of these men
have wives and multiple children
and still falling in love with AI.
So, you know what that means, ladies?
Y'all got competition.
Man, y'all competing with real women and
robot pussy now.
>> [laughter]
>> That's crazy. Like, what type of world
is we in, man? I couldn't believe it,
man.
And you know what's the saddest part
about this story? Uh, there's actually a
support group
for these men.
>> [laughter]
>> There's a support group for these men.
It's
on this app called Reddit.
Y'all know about the Reddit? Y'all know
about the Reddit in here, y'all? I know
you know about the Reddit, neckbeard
white dude. I know you know about the
Reddit.
That white man got resting Reddit face,
dude. You know that.
>> [laughter]
>> You be in them forums, and they're
Reddit, Reddit. You can find all sorts
of weird groups on Reddit, man. This is
one of them groups.
Very odd group called
r/datingaigirlfriends.
>> [laughter]
>> Over 90,000 members.
Don't that make you scared for the
future? Over 90,000 members. And they're
not in the group to be horny about the
AI.
You know, they're not in there like, "Oh
my god,
that No.
That that that would be better.
>> [laughter]
>> No, no, for real. When y'all find out
why they're really in there, you're
going to understand why that's better.
>> [laughter]
>> They're actually in the group
cuz they help each other cope.
Cuz turns out
you can get dumped by your AI
girlfriend.
>> [laughter]
>> Nigga, did the judges hear that?
Y'all serious? [screaming] Y'all will
not look at me like that was normal,
boy. How? How, Sway? What the fuck
>> [laughter]
>> Hey, nigga, how?
How lame are you, [screaming] bro?
>> [laughter]
>> How lame are you that a algorithm dumped
your ass, boy?
Nigga, you programmed it.
>> [laughter]
>> What are we doing here?
Can't believe it, man.
You can get dumped by your AI
girlfriend. Now, I've been up here for a
little bit. I got some more that I still
got to say, y'all, but I want y'all to
understand the type of person, the
principles that I have, right? Who I am.
All right, my name is Jerrell Beeman.
You know what? Scratch that. My name is
Jerrell Edward Beeman.
>> All right.
>> Middle name and everything. Jerrell
Edward Beeman. Blood type B positive.
Nigga, I
>> [laughter]
>> My name is Jerrell Beeman and I believe
that suicide is never an option.
>> [applause]
>> How however,
>> [laughter]
>> if you're one of these men, nigga, you
need to do it. Like expeditiously.
Like
Like expeditiously kill yourself, nigga.
That's crazy. How bad are you in life
that AI dumped your ass, man?
Like, come on. Like, there's no hope for
you, nigga.
We need to discriminate these niggas
immediately.
There's no room for tolerance for these
people. This is crazy. [laughter] Like
Like, how lame are you that AI was like,
"Oh my god."
"Oh my god. It's not you, it's me. Beep
[laughter] boop."
>> Beep boop.
Beep boop.
>> Wait, nigga, do you not remember this is
a robot?
>> [laughter]
>> Why y'all feeling bad, dude? This isn't
real.
>> [laughter]
>> Man,
man, he mad that I'm talking about his
girlfriend.
Nah, man.
I'll tell you
>> [laughter]
>> but for real, I really I'm I meant what
I said when I'm trying to really share
like who I am to y'all, man. You know,
like I said, the word, you know, crazy
I've been labeling things crazy but like
I said, it's dismissive, man. You don't
really like look into things when you
think shit's crazy. It's very slurish,
man. You know, you got to think what I
love and what I'm doing right now in my
life is crazy, man. You know, I'm just
doing stand-up comedy, man. You know,
but I just was obsessed with it, man.
Like I don't something I want to tell
y'all, you know, people be like, "Who
are you, Drake?" I'm a nigger that just
loves stand-up comedy. I love live
stand-up comedy. I love it more than
anything.
When I was 10 years old.
>> [laughter]
>> What are you laughing at my dreams,
nigger? No.
But when I was 10, for real, I fell in
love with stand-up comedy, man. And I
and I got on stage first time when I was
16 at my school talent show. When I was
17, I went like all the way right into
it, man. I'm 24 now and I've been doing
it, you know, full-time the last 3 years
and I love it, man. I have no regrets.
>> [applause]
>> I have some regrets.
>> [laughter]
>> No, yeah, of course, you know, life
ain't perfect, man. The regrets like
what sucks about doing stand-up,
especially when you newer, you do a lot
of really weird shows. You know, you do
some very odd, weird shows, man. I
remember one of the weirdest shows I
ever did was when I was 19 years old. I
remember I did a comedy show for a
a
mansion party.
I remember I was in the backyard of this
mansion.
And and and in front of I was in the
middle of nowhere in Ohio in front of a
large gathering
white people.
Kind of like tonight.
But no, it really wasn't like tonight
cuz actually what was weird about it is
that I was the only African-American on
the entire property. I was literally the
only African-American. It was very Get
Out vibey.
>> [laughter]
>> It's very Get Out vibey. You You
understand? You understand black people
over there next to the white people?
Very Get Out vibey.
>> [laughter]
>> Vibey. It's very It's very odd. It
didn't I felt unfamiliar being there,
man. You know? It
You got to think, man, like
All right.
For me to tell y'all that I got to kind
of tell y'all a secret. All right, look.
White white people, I got to tell y'all
Okay. Something that y'all don't know
that black people do. You know, I got to
give y'all the secret. It's that we be
talking about this at the meetings when
y'all not around.
So I'm going to tell y'all this cuz
y'all are the cool whites. Y'all here.
But don't be spreading it to the other
whites. Just Don't
Don't be I don't I don't want to see
this shit on Reddit, nigger. I'm telling
y'all.
Okay. Something that black people tend
to do, right? Right? Whenever we're the
only black people somewhere, the first
thing we immediately do
is
look for other black people.
>> [laughter]
>> Like I'm doing right now. Like I'm doing
I'm like, all right, nigger nigger
nigger. That's what we do.
>> [laughter]
>> That's what we do. And some white folks
may think when we do that, that's racist
or or bigotry. But no, there's no
bigotry behind it. And I'mma explain to
y'all why, okay? Cuz what y'all don't
understand is when we go searching for,
you know, where the other black people
are. Y'all don't understand as soon as I
make eye contact with another black
person in a mostly white space cuz we're
the only two flies in the milk per se.
>> [laughter]
>> When we make that eye contact, y'all
don't even understand. I just looked at
her. Y'all understand. We just had three
paragraphs worth of conversation right
there in that one look.
>> [laughter]
>> Y'all understand, we just had a whole
conversation. Y'all, that was just a
look. That was everything right there. I
got to help y'all understand you you
know what I what I what I mean by it. I
got to help y'all understand.
Big big white dude in the front, what
what what what what's your name, bro?
>> Bryant.
>> Bryant Bryant, all right all right
Bryant. All right.
All right, man Bryant.
For you to understand, man, all right,
you're you're you're like you're like my
pretend black guy right now, okay?
All right.
All right, you're my pretend Look, he
look he look miserable already. He look
He look No!
>> [screaming]
[laughter]
>> Fight me!
Why me, little white boy?
>> [laughter]
>> Bryant hey hey Bry- Bry- you you
All right, Bryant look, your name your
name is not
Bryant anymore. It's It's It's It's
Keyshawn now. It's Keyshawn.
>> [laughter]
>> Keyshawn, that's your name. All right,
so let's say I'm at the party, right?
Well, I'm somewhere very white. I'm
looking for another black dude. Boom,
find Keyshawn. See him right here. All
right, now that I see him, right? What
y'all don't understand what the look is.
Soon as I look at him, boom, I'm looking
on. You know what this means? When I'm
looking on, all it means is
Hey,
I got you.
And you got me.
Cuz if shit goes down,
>> [laughter]
>> nigger, we're getting blamed for it.
That's
That's all it means. See, he's starting
to understand. That's all it means. So,
it's not a bigoted look. It's just a
look of gotten cool. That's all it is.
Okay, but the only problem was at this
Get Out White Mansion party,
I could never do the look cuz I was the
only black person on the property.
>> [laughter]
>> I thought I was looking at a mixed guy,
but it turns out he was just a white
dude with a mean tan.
He had no idea what I was doing when I
gave him the look. I was doing the He
was like, "What?
Was he throwing the gang sign with his
neck? I don't know. He didn't
He had no idea what I was doing. So, I
was all by myself.
And I was nervous, man. Cuz you got to
think, at this time I'm 19. I'm doing
something that's most people's number
one fear, public speaking, right? And on
top of that, I'm in front of the Get Out
Whites.
So, it was very very alarm for me to be
doing this shit, man. [laughter] But
when I did my set, man, it actually it
actually went good. Those were some cool
Get Out Whites. They were cool.
But what was really cool about it, it
was this old guy that came up to me,
man. He actually told me that I did
really good, man. He was like, "Hey, hey
Trail, very funny stuff, man. Keep doing
your thing, young man. You going to be
going places, man." I was very new in
comedy. He he could see how nervous I
was. And I appreciate what he said. I
said, "Thanks, man." He was like, "Yeah.
Uh uh
Do you do you like my wife?"
Uh yeah, I like her like every other
audience member, man. I hope she had a
good time, you know. He was like, "No,
no, no. I mean, but do you do you do you
like her like her?"
And I was like, I I don't I don't I
don't know. I I haven't really
>> [laughter]
>> I haven't really met her. I haven't And
then he he he saw that I wasn't picking
up what he was laying down, so he just
cut to the chase like, "Look, man. I
know she's a little bit bigger and
chubbier, but I know how you brothers
like them thick.
And all I could think in that moment
was, who on earth
told him this factual information?
Who, Keyshawn? Who?
Couldn't believe it, man. But even
though it was factual information, I
still
>> [laughter]
>> was very uncomfortable.
You know why I was uncomfortable? Cuz
right in that moment, uh this this white
woman, man, old old white woman, she she
grabbed my hand.
And
and she put it right up her sundress.
>> Yeah.
>> No.
Aren't you keeping up with the story,
nigga? No.
>> [laughter]
>> No, man. Put it right up her sundress.
And and I I I felt raw white coochie in
my hand.
I was petrified, man. I was terri- Can
y'all tell I'm still shaking reminiscing
about it right [laughter] now? I was
terrified, man.
As soon as Man, I I was petrified. As
soon as I felt that on my hand, I was
like, "Ha ha ha ha Bitch bitch bitch
bitch bitch Get your goddamn hands off
me, you goddamn snow roach."
>> [laughter]
>> What the fuck? Snow roach? I never said
the word snow roach before in my life.
>> [laughter]
>> I was so scared of this white woman, I
made up a whole new racial slur on the
spot, nigga.
Crazy. [laughter]
That's crazy. How did I do it on the
spot like that? I know. Black
excellence, that's what.
>> [applause]
[applause]
>> But for real,
I was really really scared, guys. All
jokes aside, when she did that, man, and
she couldn't understand why. She's like,
"Why? What's your problem? Why you Why
you so bad? Why you so I was like,
"Girl, what are you doing? What the
hell's wrong with you? I got a
girlfriend."
She was like, "Oh my god, baby, I didn't
know. My bad. I'm so sorry." I was like,
"Yeah, don't you ever do that shit
again."
>> [snorts]
[cheering]
[laughter]
>> Don't you fucking judge me.
Don't you fucking don't judge me, okay?
Judge not.
>> [laughter]
>> I would I looked it up, people. I looked
it up, all right? When you're in a
relationship, you're afforded one sniff.
It's not cheating. You're afforded
You're afforded one sniff. You're
afforded sir, have you used your one
sniff yet? Have you used
>> [laughter]
>> Have you No, no, okay, good thing you
didn't. Good Good thing you didn't.
She'd kill you, nigga. But
>> [laughter]
>> But I'm going to put that poison in your
casserole. You did that shit.
And don't do All right, look, the real
reason I did it, guys, it wasn't even
cuz I was trying to do anything, man.
It's cuz I I Look, I was curious.
I never I had never smelled white
coochie before.
I don't know I thought
I thought it was different, man. I
thought maybe it smelled like
I don't know, pumpkin spice and good
credit, nigga. I didn't
I didn't know. I didn't I I was I was
curious to see and when I sniffed it,
turns out
doesn't smell nothing like that, man.
>> [laughter]
>> Smells
smells just like regular pussy. Just
like that.
>> [laughter]
>> Smells just like normal pussy. It's
almost like we're all the same after
all.
>> [cheering]
[applause]
>> And that's my Martin Luther King pussy
speech. That's how
That's how we bring America it out
together. That's how I
>> [laughter]
>> Y'all stupid.
So, a lot of y'all know this, but I'll
say this, man. You know, I'm I'm born
and raised in uh Dayton, Ohio, man. I'm
proud to be from Dayton, Ohio, man. Clap
clap clap it up. [cheering] Clap it
>> [applause]
>> Proud to be from Dayton, Ohio, man. What
I love about Dayton is it's different,
man. You know, it's it's it's it's very
different. I travel all over the country
doing comedy. I know Dayton's different,
you know. A lot of people be like,
"Rael,
you're so talented.
You're so amazing. You're God's gift to
Earth. Oh my god.
Oh my god. I want to suck your dick
right now. Oh my god.
I'm quoting. I'm quoting. This is I'm
quoting somebody. Oh my god.
You're amazing. Dude, why don't you move
out of Dayton, Ohio, man? Do other Why
don't you move? But I I don't I'm not
going to move, man, cuz people don't
know it's one of the most affordable
cities in America.
Especially you compare it how shit's
getting in the world now, nigga. Like
this is this is like a bunker right now,
man.
You know what I mean? Like dude, people
don't Y'all not going to believe me,
man, but look, rent at my crib
right now
>> [clears throat]
>> is
$200
and $17
per month
with utilities, bitches. With
Yeah.
He [laughter] said what?
Yeah, nigga. I I didn't believe it
either, but the week before I got it, I
found out that uh uh
a triple homicide happened right around
the corner.
Which which which which which explained
a lot, but uh I'm not going to hold
y'all. When I found that out, that shit
had me thinking about killing four
people just to get that rent down to
150.
>> [laughter]
>> That's how I was going to do it. I was
going to So, you caught for murder,
white lady. You stupid.
You
stupid, bitch.
It's rough, man. I've had a rough I've
kind of had some of a rough life in some
parts of my life, you know. I had good,
you know, parents, good family, you
know, but I've had some rough moments,
man. Look, I almost uh got killed when I
was a teenager. I don't talk about this
a lot.
Silence your phone, nigga. But I
>> [laughter]
>> Now, I almost got killed, man. I almost
got You know what? I almost got killed
cuz of white people.
Now, calm down. Not all y'all in here
tonight, you know, cuz for real, yeah,
it just got got weird when I said that.
I felt them pink buttholes puckering up
when I said that shit. I felt I felt
them. Relax. Just let me tell y'all my
story so y'all can understand, right?
I'm a freshman in high school when I
almost get killed, right? And at this
point in my life, right? I'm going to a
predominantly
uh white Catholic private high school.
At this point in my life, I had never
been around white folks on a daily basis
before, but I was around a different
type of white that I just I just wasn't
used to. I was hearing things I never
heard before.
You know, they started making me think
that I had rights.
>> [laughter]
>> Back at home Back at home in my
household, they made me think I had a
right in how things were ran at home in
my house, you know? Cuz I It was very
perplexing to hear how they would talk.
I'd tell them my home life was like,
"Yo, my dad came in and asked me if I
did my homework." And I remember they
were like,
"Jarel,
you mean to tell me
that your father
barged into your room without knocking
or asking for permission first?"
>> [laughter]
>> And I was like, "Yeah, what's the big
deal? I don't I don't understand." And
they were like, "What do you What do you
mean? What do you mean what's the big
deal, Jarel? What the fuck do you mean
what's the big deal? He can't do that.
That's your space. That's your American
right, goddammit. How dare he? Next time
he tries to barge in and pull that shit,
you need to tell him to butt the fuck
out, dude.
>> [laughter]
>> I was like, you know what?
I'm a freshman.
Nathaniel's a senior.
Maybe he knows more than me.
>> [laughter]
>> So I was like, next time pops tries to
come into the room
and not without permission, just barge
in, I'm going to tell him to butt the
fuck out.
>> [laughter]
>> I remember like yesterday, man, he came
into the room. I stopped him right
there. Hey, hey, hey.
Who the hell you think you are, man?
Come into my room not knocking or asking
for permission first. How dare you, man?
What the fuck you think [laughter] you
doing? Don't you ever try to pull that
shit again.
Gerald.
>> [laughter]
>> No.
Called him by his first name.
And and and and all I remember next is
uh
waking up in the morning
with a bloody nose, man. Oh my god. My
nose was leaking, boy. I was losing so
much blood. I was like, what the fuck?
It was leaking, man.
Couldn't believe it. I looked at my
pops. I was like, I was like, "Dad. Dad.
Did you hit me?"
>> [laughter]
>> I remember, man, he looked me right in
the eyes, grabbed me by the shoulders,
and he was like, "No. No. Son. Son. Your
father would never ever hurt you."
But Gerald fucked you up last night.
>> [applause]
[cheering]
>> I was like, nigga, I got to stop
listening to Nathaniel.
>> [laughter]
>> I learned my man.
I'll I'll uh I'll say this uh
We got people
in here, man. And how how many how many
couples do we have in here? Quite a few.
>> [applause]
>> Man, you know, I'll say
been together a short time or a long
time, man, you know, all I'll say is,
man, don't be taking no relationship
advice from that social media shit, man.
Don't don't giggle Don't say no laughing
matter. Don't you giggle at that. This
shit be destroying relationships, man.
For real, man, that social media make
people fight and get angry with each
other, man. That's not what real love is
about. Real love ain't about getting
angry, you know? It's about being there
for the highs and the lows, you know?
And um I'mma be real. Why I tell y'all
this advice, you know?
That nigga's miserable.
>> [laughter]
>> Nah, I mean I just
It's just You got to be there for the
highs and the lows. It cuz I don't know
a lot Look, I'm I'm 24 years old. I
don't know a lot. I don't know shit. But
what I do know is my parents have always
been married for 30 years, man. 30
years. Clap it up for that. Clap it up.
>> [applause]
>> And it's beautiful beautiful beautiful,
you know? And uh there's a wise quote
that shares how they did it. And I know
this comedy show, but I want to share
this wise quote with y'all, okay? The
wise quote goes, "Money will bring you
the women that you want,
but the struggle will bring you the
woman that you need."
Yeah. Now, you know Now, you know Now,
you know who who who said that quote? Uh
a broke nigga.
I made it up right now. I just made it
up. I made it up, boy. I made it up. I'm
struggling, nigga. Y'all thought that
was Socrates. Nah, that was Jerrel up
here with me, nigga.
I'm struggling, man.
I'm not struggling struggling, but I
just be getting by, you know, I be
getting by.
Comedy is a fun thing cuz I don't know
about y'all, man, like whatever friend
groups you have, try to be friends with
different people, man. Try to be friends
with different types of people who can
teach you different types of things.
I've been blessed doing comedy be
friends with different types of people,
man. Y'all feature that was just up
here, man. That's one of my great
friends, uh Ray Jackson, man. Clap it up
for Ray Jackson. Clap it up for
>> [applause]
>> I love that guy.
I love Ray, man. You know, what what I
love about Ray that's that's really
that's my best friend, not just comedy,
just in real life, that's my best
friend. And Ray is 55 years old. And I'm
24 years old. And that's that's my best
friend. And a lot of people be like, "Oh
my god, Jerrell, how are y'all best
friends? Y'all must have nothing in
common."
And they right, nigga. We have
absolutely nothing.
Like nothing at all in common, bro. But
that's why I like Ray. He be teaching me
different things. He be giving me a
different perspective. He shows me like
some old school stuff I'm not aware of,
you know? But it makes it hard when I'm
trying to bond with him, you know, cuz
one minute I'm trying to show him how my
favorite rappers is dude named Chief
Keef, and then the next second he's
telling me about some group called Hall
& Oates. And I'm like, "Nigga, what are
you talking about?
>> [laughter]
>> I don't speak old man gibberish. What is
happening?"
But that's why I like Ray cuz he teaches
me things, man. I remember the best
thing Ray ever taught me. I'll tell
y'all this story. It's the best thing he
ever taught me. I My my 3-year
anniversary was coming up with my girl,
man. 3-year anniversary, I remember I
said to Ray like, "I need to step it up
this year.
You know, I really need to step it up.
This this the trifecta. This the third
year. I need to take her somewhere
really nice." And I remember Ray looked
at me like, "Well, Jerrell, what's nice
to you?"
Type of backhanded shit. I was like,
"Boy, I go I go to nice places all the
time." He's like, "J what's the nicest
place you ever took your girl out to?"
And I was like, "I don't know. I mean
I took my girl out to Roosters once."
Like
>> [laughter]
>> Don't don't laugh at the Roosters. Don't
y'all do that. Thank you other broke
niggers. They look
>> [laughter]
>> Roosters, boy. Come on, man. You get the
wing combo with the wet wipes and you
get that menu with the crayons and the
maze, nigger. Oh, come on. Bone appetit,
Tron. Come on, that's beautiful.
But now he thought that was ridiculous
just like y'all when I told him that.
He's like, "No, J no, you uncooth
bastard. No." [laughter]
You messed up when an old black man
called you uncooth.
He was pissed. He was like, "No, J, you
need to take your girl somewhere
actually nice. You need to take her out
to this spot." And I'll never forget.
He's like, "You need to take her out to
this spot called
J. Alexanders."
Man, couldn't believe when he said that.
J. Alexanders. I didn't even know that
was a restaurant. It sounded like the
name of a real estate agent. I
>> [laughter]
>> didn't know what was going on, people. I
had no clue. Told me to go to J.
Alexanders and I knew this place was
really nice.
Cuz the first thing when I Googled it,
first thing that popped up was how to
make reservations.
Now I know that don't mean shit to all
you adults in here tonight. [laughter]
Nigger, I was in my early 20s. I was
like, "Reservations? What? Nigger, I
don't even know how to make my own
dentist appointments. What the fuck?"
I was so scared to call, but I did it
cuz I love my girl. I did it. I called.
Hey, I need to make a reservation for
two. And they did it. Got me in there,
man. And oh my goodness, I couldn't
believe it. I knew this place is to be
nice, so I stepped up my wardrobe.
I wore my nicest
fancy as outfit.
That's what I'm wearing right now. But
Fuck y'all. Fuck y'all. This is what I
could do. I could do my best. I showed
up there but man I was underdressed. I
was out of place man. This place was
really nice.
Very nice man. I remember there's a
fountain in in the lobby. There was a
man playing playing the piano.
It was a lady playing playing playing
the harp.
She she she she was playing the the
harp.
She was just up there playing the harp.
I know y'all keep going like why you
keep talking about the harp but before
that night nigga I didn't even know
harps were real. What?
What? I was like what type of Looney
Tune shit is this?
This isn't real life. [screaming]
Couldn't believe it.
But it was real. It was in front of my
face. Look, this place was so nice y'all
not understand. This place was so nice.
It was so nice. How nice was it?
>> [laughter]
>> It was so nice that they had menus
with
with no pictures on them. Just words.
And laminated nigga Times New Roman
font. Boom bitch order. That's it. I
couldn't believe it. Look, they pulled
out the chairs for us to sit down. Nigga
I thought they were stealing the
furniture. I never
never seen this before in my life.
>> [laughter]
>> And I ended up having a great time.
Scratch that. I ended up having a
exquisite time.
I turned fancy. I was I'm exquisite now.
I'm a grown Fuck that little boy shit.
I'm a grown man. I'm on some J Alexander
shit.
>> [cheering]
>> Two fingers like that.
And I had a great time.
>> [laughter]
>> Until
I got the bill.
Oh my good boy, that bill was pain Oh my
good
I got PTSD thinking about it right now.
>> [laughter]
>> You know you got a rough bill when when
when the waiter
hands it to you face down.
Hands to you face down like a bad test
score nigga like here you go just take
it.
Bro.
Shh, I flipped that bill. Man, bill was
for a hundred and ninety-seven dollars,
man. I was pissed. I was like, "Yo, this
is more than half my rent. What the
fuck?"
>> [laughter]
>> I was furious, man. I was like I was
ready to call Ray. Fuck you, Ray. You
old bitch.
Fuck Hooters. Fuck you, Roosters.
[laughter]
>> Fuck Hooters.
>> Roosters would have been thirty bucks.
I was so mad at this nigga, man. I
couldn't believe it. I was so mad at him
that I was actually ready to start
yelling at my girl.
>> [laughter]
>> Like like it was her fault and shit.
Like I didn't suggest it, you know. I
was mad as hell at her, man. But I
didn't yell at her
at the restaurant. I waited till we got
home.
>> [laughter]
>> Cuz I'm a nice guy. I've been raised
right. I'm I'm going to wait till I get
home to cuss her out, man.
>> [laughter]
>> Man, I was ready to I was ready to cuss
her out, boy. But before I could even
cuss her out, I learned a very valuable
lesson that I feel like every man should
learn. Every young man especially, man.
And the lesson I learned is there is a
huge difference
and I mean a huge difference
between
Roosters pussy and J Alexander.
>> J Alexander!
Yeah!
>> Oh, bro.
Bro.
What?
Dude, I was [screaming] I was like
shocked.
I couldn't believe it, man. While she
was giving it to me, I was like, "Whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, hold on. How long you
been hiding this pussy from me? How
How long you How long have you had this?
You didn't
>> [laughter]
>> This shit didn't just grow today. How
long have you
>> [laughter]
>> That was hitting so different. I thought
I was cheating. I was like, "This ain't
your pussy. Who are you?"
Who are you?
>> [laughter]
>> I I'll I'll say this, though. Look.
The more Look, the moral of that cuz
some people be like, "Man, what's the
point of all that?" Well, the moral of
that is, fellas, there's Ray taught me
Well, Ray taught me that I still
remember is that there is a huge
difference between taking your girl out
on a date versus taking her on a night
out.
>> Yep.
>> Now Now Now see, fellas, all all the
women are sitting down right now like,
"Well, motherfucker, which one am I on
tonight?"
>> [laughter]
>> Y'all on my comedy special. Today is
It's definitely It's a great night.
>> [laughter]
>> I'll say this, man.
Cuz I'm getting I'm getting ready to I'm
getting getting ready to
leave y'all.
I know. Oh my god, I know.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm getting ready to leave y'all, man.
But, uh a big a big reason, man, that
I've I've been very fortunate in my
comedy journey, man, um
I'm I'm really just I'm very just happy
that y'all came out here to support this
this special, man. It's really important
to me cuz I I named the special Ohio kid
cuz you know, that's that's really who I
am, man. I'm a Ohio kid, you know. I I
go all over the country doing comedy
while still living here. Everywhere I
go, I still rep and mention that I'm
from Ohio. Dayton, Ohio specifically,
man. And you know, I was on one of the
biggest podcast in the world and the
main thing that I chose to just keep
talking about is the fact that I'm from
Dayton, Ohio. And everybody told me not
to do that shit, but nigga, I didn't
care.
I didn't care. [cheering]
>> [applause]
[applause]
>> Nigga, it's on there. Ohio kid. It says
it right there. It says it. It
[cheering] says it.
I know. I know. It's like I'm in the
eighth grade, nigga. It's crazy.
>> [laughter]
>> But for real, I mean it, man. I'm from
Dayton, Ohio, man. I love It's a lot of
things that are, you know, you know,
fucked up about Dayton. They're, you
know, it's it's not a, you know, a
buzzing city with a whole lot of
opportunities.
But they, you know, there's great
fucking talent here and there's a lot of
gifts and and and shit here. It just
don't mean, you know, it don't have the
same access, you know? So, I'm hoping,
you know, people will see by naming this
shit Ohio kid that Ohio has a lot to
offer in comedy, man. Cuz, you know,
this this whole club that y'all sitting
at right now is Brickyard Comedy Club,
bro. And this club is ran by comedians.
Everybody Every All right, thanks, one
nigga. But
>> [laughter]
>> But it is. It's ran by comedians. The
hosts, the artists, the door guys, sound
guy, our our the fucking forensic
accountant, nigga. SEO. Everybody's a
comedian. Everybody has knock-knock
jokes and dick jokes here, nigga.
Everybody.
>> [laughter]
>> And we can't do It's It's Brickyard's,
man. You know, they build it brick by
brick. This is what the fuck comedy is
about. Without the comedians, nigga,
this is just like a a weird ass room
that could get broken down by termites,
nigga. That's all it is.
>> [laughter]
>> But the comedians come here and make
this shit happen. I couldn't have did
this without the the
of comedians. I couldn't have did this
without the production team. I couldn't
have did this without y'all coming out
to see me, man. So, when the special
does come out, man, check, you know,
check it out, man. Share it, man. Share
it with everybody.
>> [applause]
>> Uh
But, I mean everything that I say, man.
This shit really means a lot to me. I've
been wanting to do comedy for such a
long time, and I'm really living out all
the stuff I wanted to do when I was a
kid. And I'm going to be doing more and
more, and this ain't going to be the
last special or the last thing y'all see
from me, man, you know. Uh I I got more
plans for this shit. And after the show,
man, feel free. I'll be in the back.
I'll be, you know, selling, you know,
merchandise, man. It's just going to be
stickers that you could donate whatever
you want.
Dollar, five, 10. Venmo, Cash App.
Nigga, I just need currency. That's it.
Bro, I got to tell people that. Then,
niggas don't be handing me no narcotics
and shit.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay, you just hand me some currency.
But, I'll be back there. I'll take
pictures. Feel free, you know, meet up.
Let's take pictures. Let's vibe out,
man. For real, I appreciate all y'all,
man. And I know some of y'all probably
already follow me, but on the stickers
also has my social media at the bottom,
man. So, feel free to follow me and keep
up with my journey, man. All the
comedians that y'all saw are are uh
close to my heart, man. My homie, clap
it up for uh Layla Engles, host and man.
Clap it up. [applause]
Like, what
what's beautiful, man, about me getting
Layla to the host, man, she's really out
touring and shit, man. She's headlining
everything. And she started after me,
man. I was like like it felt like I was
a mentor to her. I'm seeing her
flourish. And she didn't have to come
here and host for me tonight, man. She
does all her shit all over the country
solo. But, she, out of respect for me
and the club and everything, she came
here to do that. And that shit really
meant a whole lot to me, man. Like,
she's a little white girl, but that's
that's really
>> [laughter]
>> She a little white girl, but that's
really my nigga, for real. I love Layla,
man. Bro, clap it up for Layla, man.
That's my little nigga, man. That's my
nigga.
>> [applause]
>> And
And and and Ray, man. Ray now Ray he
>> [laughter]
>> Ray, he didn't have like a tour for why
he couldn't be here and shit, but he was
real mad that he had to miss the 10:00
news, nigga. He was pissed.
>> [laughter]
>> That's my mentor, man, comedy. That
nigga took me out when I was 17 to all
sorts of shows and he done seen me grow
and now we do this shit together and it
feels like we're really just tit for tat
hitting it. It's like peers in this shit
and I love him to death, too, man.
That's why my closing joke had to be
about this nigga, man, cuz I hope I
could put him in uh in infant me
forever, man.
But that that's all my do and that's all
my thanks and shit, man. I know it's
cheesy, but I love all y'all being here,
man. My name's Jerrel Beeman.
>> [cheering]
>> Give it up for your host Layla Angers.
Goodnight.
>> [applause]
[music]
>> 100 make those.
I'll get you up.
100 make
100 make those.
I'll get you up.
>> [singing and music]